# **RESUME (TGT SCIENCE)**

Email id: bhagatanchal26@gmail.com

Mobile: 9878677568



### **OBJECTIVE:**

To become a dynamic, distinguished and popular part of an institution that provides me an opportunity to apply the skills and creativity that I have acquired, generating results through teamwork, trust and respect for all those contributing "Work is Worship, Duty is God", that is what I believe in. As hard work is always needed for successful results so hard work is my passion with progressive and positive attitude as my strength. In addition to this have a zest to battle against the odds in life & excel by achieving targets and to gain from the experiences of seniors and subordinates.

#### **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND:**

COURSE	YEAR OF PASSING	BOARD/ UNIVERSITY
B. Ed.	2014	Panjab University
M.Sc. (Chemistry)	2016	Panjab University
B.Sc.	2013	Panjab University
10+2	2009	P.S.E.B
10 <sup>th</sup>	2007	P.S.E.B
PDPET(6 Months Bridge Course)	2019	NIOS

### **EXPERIENCE:-**

- 1. Worked as a Science Teacher in DCM Group of Schools firozpur city from April 2017 to January 2020 approx 3 years.
- 2. Worked as TGT SCIENCE (CHEMISTRY) in DCM Group of Schools from 4<sup>th</sup> October, 2021 to 3<sup>rd</sup> June 2023.
- 3. Worked as a coordinator in DCM Group of schools from 4<sup>th</sup> October, 2021 to 3<sup>rd</sup> June 2023.
- 4. Appointed as Evaluator for Subject Science (Code 086) for Term II for session 2021-22 & Yearly Session 2022- 2023 also

### WORKSHOPS ATTENDED:

Sr. No.	Workshop	No. of Days
1.	Capacity Building Programme in Science (CBSE)	2
2.	Life Skills (CBSE)	1
3.	Design thinking and innovation Workshop	1
	(Creya)	
4.	Capacity Building Workshop on Stem Education,	1

	design thinking , Experiential learning and inquiry based learning ( CBSE)	
5.	Microsoft Workshop	1+1
6.	Workshop by Millennium	1
7.	Gender Equality	1
8.	Effective teaching	1
9.	Child Abuse	1
10.	Workshop on Science Practicals	1

**TECHNICAL SKILLS:-** Basic and Microsoft Expert.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS:- Money Smart Teacher (Completed Financial Education Training Program conducted by National Centre for Financial Education, NCFE)

**SOFTSKILLS:**- GoodCommunicationSkills,Adaptable,LeadershipSkills,Highlyresponsible.

**HOBBIES:-** Listening Music, ReadingBooks.

### **PERSONAL DETAILS:**

Father's Name : Sh.Madanjit

Mother' Name : Smt. Tripta

Date of Birth : 26 November, 1991

Marital Status : Married Sex : Female

Languages Known: English, Hindi and Punjabi

### **REFERENCES**

- 1. Ms. Yachna Chawla, Principal, DCM Sen Sec Schools, Ferozepur, Phone no. 9876053832
- 2. Mr. Manish Banga, Deputy Principal, DCM Group of Schools, Ferozepur, Phone no. 9855435309
- 3. Mr. Rajesh Kumar Chandel , Principal , Dass and Brown World School, Ferozepur, 8817710000

## **DECLARATION:**

I hereby declare that the information given above is true to the best of my knowledge.

(Anchal Bhagat)